

Thu Hang Le

Graduate Statistician/ Data Analyst

My Contact

Marsfield, NSW 2122



🗹 hanglth@gmail.com



mana-le.com



in linkedin.com/in/hanglth



🦙 github.com/Hana-Le

Education Background

- Macquarie University Masters of Applied Statistics Completed in Dec 2022 **WAM 85**
- University of Queensland Master of Project Management
- Vietnam National University, Hanoi Bachelor of Science

Technical Skills

- R
- SOL
- Tableau
- Excel Data Analysis
- Python
- Data Visualisation
- · Statistical Modeling
- · Data Analysis

Soft Skills

- Skilled in stakeholder partnership management across sectors
- Adaptable to diverse working styles
- Experienced in diverse team collaboration
- Solution-focused and data-driven

About Me

A recent Applied Statistics graduate with a WAM of 85 and a passion for utilizing computational techniques to analyze and interpret data. Proficient in R, SQL, Tableau, and Excel with in-depth knowledge of contemporary statistical methods. Seeking opportunities to further develop skills and bring 6+ years of project management experience in UN and NGO settings, including data collection and analysis, to the table.

Professional Experience

Avant Mutual | Data Entry Officer

2022 (casual)

Key responsibilities:

Reviewing, verifying and compiling data in the database system.

Oxfam in Viet Nam | Program Officer

2018 - 2019

Key responsibilities:

Design and implementation management of a series of gender and development projects, delivered in partnership with both nongovernment organisations and government agencies.

International Labour Organization | Project Coordinator

2015 - 2017

Key responsibilities:

Implementation management of a USD1.5m portfolio of projects aimed at improving labour practices in private sector enterprises in Viet Nam.

Care int. in Viet Nam | Project Manager

2010 - 2014

Key responsibilities:

Implementation management of a USD1m portfolio of projects aimed at delivering public health interventions for disadvantaged and vulnerable communities.

Achievements

- · Successfully managed all projects in charge, including delivering on time, within budget, and to the agreed quality specifications.
- · Achieved a full scholarship for the master's program at Queensland University.